tribalpages.com 2017-07-29

# Privacy Statement

## Privacy Statement for TribalPages 

**TribalPages** has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site: [TribalPages ](https://www.tribalpages.com/)

#### Cookies 

Our Site uses cookies to maintain member's session when they log in.

#### Advertisers 

We use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information. 

#### Registration Forms 

Our site's registration form requires users to give us contact information (like their name and email).

The members contact information is also used to get in touch with the customer when necessary. 

#### Children's Guidelines 

This site **DOES NOT MEET** the Online Privacy Protection Act guidelines The following criteria are violated: 

  1. This site allows children to post or distribute any personally identifiable information without first obtaining verifiable parental consent. 
  2. This site does not encourage children to get their parent's permission before sharing personal information online. 

#### Data Quality/Access 

This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided: 

  1. You can visit the following URL: <https://www.tribalpages.com/>

## Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact:   

* * *

Generated by [Privacy Wizard](https://privacy.linkexchange.com/)
